

### Contact

- + 48 664 447 556
- Poland/Katowice
- daniel-kowalski.com
- ( k0wal45

## **Tech Stack**

HTML CSS

JavaScript

React JS

Next JS

Tailwind CSS

TypeScript

Redux

MySQL

## Languages

Polish - native English - B2/C1

# Additional Skills

Driver's Licence Graphic Design Local Networks Operating Systems

# **Education**

**ZSTIO 2 - IT** 09.2019 - 05.2024

Politechnika Śląska - IT start - 10.2024

# **Daniel Kowalski**

### Front-end developer

### About me

Hi! I'm a 20-year-old front-end developer who began exploring web development during a 2022 internship at Kyndryl. In my final year of school, I teamed up with friends to tackle a cybersecurity project. Now, I'm excited to start a new chapter at Politechnika Śląska. In my free time, I enjoy collecting LEGO and traveling around Europe, with hopes to explore the world in the future.

# **Experience**

### Kyndryl - Internship

11.2022 (1 month)

This internship was my first experience working in a corporation. We learned about SCRUM, Agile, and the various rules and principles that govern work in a company of this size. Additionally, we had some lectures about mainframes which was continuation of lectures in school and had the pleasure of meeting many specialists.

#### Kyndryl - Logistics and IT support assistant

02.2023 - 08.2023

After completing my apprenticeship, I applied for a position to assist with IT and office tasks at Kyndryl and was accepted once the department opened. My responsibilities included helping coworkers with their computers. The work was varied and flexible, requiring strong problem-solving abilities and logical thinking.

### Lunarisweb.pl - Freelance

03.2023 - present

Driven by my web development skills and ambitions, I decided to pursue freelance work. I've collaborated with companies in various fields, including transport and healthcare. Throughout these projects, I've utilized tools and technologies such as Next.js, Sanity CMS, WordPress, as well as Inkscape and GIMP for logo design and advertisements.

# **Projects**

### Bezpieczni w teorii - bezpieczni wteorii.pl

11.2023 - 05.2024

I was responsible for the entire graphic design and marketing of the project. I created the logo, built the website in React.js, and handled all the posts. The project focused on cybersecurity, and we organized lectures featuring specialists from companies like ING Bank Śląski, Kyndryl or Revolut. Project qualified for the finals of the olympiad

#### Lunaris UI - ui.lunarisweb.pl

08.2024 - present

When I create websites for my clients in my freelance career, I save time by using prebuilt components that I developed earlier. I realized I could make these open-source to help others on their journey.

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji